# Michael Hoang Tran

Salt Lake City, Utah, US | +1 (801) 634-7693 | michaeltranperson@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/michael-tran-20462112a/ | mikesenh.com

### **SUMMARY**

I have been working professionally as a Designer for 2 years and as a Developer for 1 year. I have a deep appreciation for both development and design, recognizing the importance of their synergy. I am driven by a passion for continuous learning, creative endeavors, and making a significant impact in the world while positively enriching people's lives.

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

- Programming: HTML,CSS, JavaScript, Python, PHP
- Database Management: MySQL
- UX: User Research, Information Architecture, User Focused Design
- Frameworks / Libraries: Laravel, Svelte, SvelteKit, TailwindCSS, Bootstrap, Bulma
- Designed: Photo Editing, Video Editing, Figma: Prototyping and Mockup

### **SOFT SKILLS**

 Effective Time Management, Detail Tracking of Assignments, Organizing Data, Customer Focus Mindset and Going Above and Beyond to Achieve Satisfaction.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# The Grace Company, Web Designer / Developer

2022 - 2023

• I played a vital role in the redesign of the website, which resulted in unprecedented online sales, serving as a remarkable milestone in the company's history.

## Janadhi & Company, Web Designer

2021 - 2022

• I gained hands-on experience in the process of designing and constructing mockup prototypes, which involved translating the company's vision into tangible websites.

#### **EDUCATION**

# Weber State University, Bachelor of Science - Web and User Experience

2020 - 2022

- Enphase on Full-Stack Web Development
- CP: User Experience Design
- Honors: Summa Cum Laude

## SLCC, Associate of Science - Computer Sci and Information Systems

2017 - 2020

- CP: Web Programming & Development
- CP: Computer Science Fundamentals

# Michael Hoang Tran

Salt Lake City, Utah, US | +1 (801) 634-7693 | michaeltranperson@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/michael-tran-20462112a/ | mikesenh.com

## **REFERENCES**

# Christina Delima - UX/Product Designer & Visual Designer

Kihei, Hawaii, United States (808) 268-6520 | info@christinashayne.com

## **Austin Wilcox - Senior Software Developer**

Ogden, Utah, United States
(801) 430-5239 | Me@theaustinwilcox.com

# **Zachery Fauver - Graphic Designer**

Salt Lake City, Utah, United States (435) 630-9000 | fauverz@gmail.com

## Justice Daniels - Marketing Manager

Salt Lake City, Utah, United States (385) 423-1563 | justicedaniels1@gmail.com